The value of R^2 will be = 1 - SSres(the sum average of the regression)/SStot(the sum average of the y averages)
supposed to be an answer between 0 and 1, the closer to 1 will indicate that the predicted values will be more accurate.
1 = perfect(suspicious)
0.9~ = very good
0.7> = not great
0.4> = terrible
0> = makes no sense for this data

adjusted R^2
we are looking the minimize the SSres(method called Ordinary least squares) and so if we add to the equation to calculate
y^ another parameter (b3*X3) if the value it gives us will make the regression worse and not better we'll pick b3=0 so the
regression will stay the same instead of getting worse, so this regression can only improve or stay the same for any parameters
added.
the formula to correct it: 1-(1-R)^2* (n-1)/(n-k-1)
where: n = sample size, k = number of independent variables
so when k increses, the fraction is getting smaller and affects the equation to go down.

the usage of R in the code:

from sklearn.metrics import r2_score
r2_score(y_test, y_pred)

comparing the actual values of the dependent variable with the predicted ones. we will want to run it on every
module we have and see which one gives us the best R^2 values, and that will be the best module we can use.